how we doing?
>> Thanks very much, guys.
>> It wasn't easy. I don't think any game's
easy. I think um you go out there and
you look at who they are and how you
have to approach them whilst being
yourself. And I thought we put a plan
together, me and Mike and the other
coaches, um, CP Hines, K Scott, Jeff
Howard, and the guys executed at elite
level.
>> Yeah, I'll be honest with you, like it's
still kind of settling in. Um, with
regards to like who won it, it's from
our perspective, it don't feel like
that. I feel like this Mike has created
a team and um it's truly that that as a
collective we won the game.
>> 2011.
>> No, no, I just um the only thing I would
say I feel is grateful. I just feel like
I think as you go through these
journeys, the people that help you get
lost along the way, the people that have
supported you and a lot of people have
sacrificed a lot for me to be sitting
here, but you don't see all the people
around me that helped me get here. And
um I'm just very grateful for them.
>> Yeah. Like it that's that's one of the
the um coolest things is that you you
get to like reconnect with a lot of
people cuz like just people I've had
random people text me from like that I
met like four or five years ago. It's
just good to reconnect with them.
>> Um
n just friends and old friends.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's one of my close friends.
got many people staying up to watch a
game.
>> Yeah, I think my mom I think my mom and
my brother watched the game at um a
skuss like an NFL party and that my when
my son and wife sons and wife came on
the field they showed me a picture of
them at the game. So that was pretty
cool.
>> Um
I think when we when we came here as a
um as a collective of coaches like one
of our main focuses were to enhance the
players and make them play as well as
they possibly can. When you got players
like Leo, Byron, Nick, Spoon, Daw,
Chenna, Dehaw, like once they start
playing with great fundamentals, it
gives you the ability to do a lot of
those things like play the run and split
safety, be able to stop explosive plays
and then suddenly what happens is like
tonight was just about rushing covering.
Like we had some good blitzes dialed up
and we executed them well, but like you
saw like at times someone had a quick
win, they got to the call back. times
they held the they held the um they made
the quartback hold the ball and we
sacked the quarterback. Like that
collective and that connection as a
defense really took us to the next
level.
>> As an example, like on the play when
the ball has to go right for him to come
like who's doing what the ball on the
line like all goes into that?
>> Yeah, like it's a good question. Like
everyone has the guys that are rushing
and blitzing, everyone has a specific
movement and they have to win in that
specific way and they all did and um
Spoon came free and rushed. He reached
and poked the ball and it just it
blessed Chenner, hit him straight in the
chest.
>> Is there any like job a guy has like
particular interest that you would not
be able to see that you can share with
us as far as
>> I just think like as it's like a a guy
has a high rush on the outside. I think
um it came from it came from the field.
So EJ has to go up and under the um
whoever's blocking him and then Spoon
comes through.
>> When you were um meeting with your team
for the last two weeks, what were the
biggest points of emphasis for you as
far as game plan or
>> the number one thing was we have to be
who we are. That's it. Like what like
guys in this room that you're hearing
talking right now like they played an
extremely high level down in down out
for the whole season. And the number one
message from all of us, especially Mike,
was just be us. And um I thought they've
done that tonight.
Yeah, I think like one you're you have
to be who you are to to do anything
because you have to have principles to
stand on, but like you might say I
haven't grown up with the sport, but
like I've loved the sport since I was a
kid. So like in my mind, I've grown up
with the sport and it might not have
been the same way someone else grew up
with the sport, but this is the thing
I've loved like outside as a as a um as
a sport, as something I played from when
I was young.
What's up?
>> Congratulations.
>> When did you see the game come to
>> from down one? Like I thought I thought
the guys
they I thought yesterday at practice we
had an unbelievable practice. It was
locked in. It was a walk through. The
communication was great. The body
position was great. It makes you come
off as a coach feeling great. And then
like you go into the meetings and you go
into the locker room and you see the
guys and it just gives you confidence.
>> You know how it played out. We don't
have to say much about that. you
mentioned.
>> Yeah, it was um when I remember they
came running in from the um we was down
the end where Mike's podium where
Michael was on the podium and they came
running in. I just hugged them like just
to see my boys and see the enjoyment
that they get from that moment. My my
oldest son called me in a week and he
was like my bucket list was going to see
the Super Bowl and I got to see my dad
in the Super Bowl and I was like that's
the coolest thing I've heard in a long
time.
>> I'm curious how you did that this week
and how important you thought that was.
>> Yeah, I think like when when you get
like we call it like a l loose and
focused mindset is like when you get to
that point that work isn't done this
week. that works done like in offseason
through training camp when when you go
through rough times when you go through
great times you have to be the same
person and Mike does an unbelievable job
of being the same guy week in week out I
think we have a um we have a clear
understanding that like if you create an
environment that everyone loves coming
to work they're going to be the best
version of themselves and Mike has done
that
>> you mentioned the message was be who you
are how would you describe you know who
this defense
um fast, physical, full hungry and they
work as a collective to rush and cover.
>> A lot of pride.
>> Yeah. I think it's I think like
it's just to come from like London and
be here and be in front of you guys. cuz
I don't take any of that for granted and
I don't like
it's I'm just I'm proud.
>> Yeah, thank you. Because normally I
would have fallen asleep at halftime.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I got to get back to London
like get this mayhem out of the way and
I need to go home.
>> What's up then?
It's cool. It's like like um it I think
the guy you just have to give credit to
the players like they made a commitment
day one to be the best in the world and
they set a goal and to achieve goals
they have to do it every day and they
have to keep each other accountable.
they have to do all the stuff that's
really hard and they chose to do it and
through Mike's leadership and um all the
coaches that coach them as hard as we
were saying in the meeting the other day
that like the coaches all they do is try
and put these guys in the best position.
We stay up late to do those things and
everyone just owned their role at the
best they could possibly do it and it's
just we got the outcome we wanted.
>> What did it mean to see the game? H it
meant for me it meant the world. But
like um for him I was just so proud of
him. Like I think that that group up
front like they knew they had to come in
and it had to be the most unselfish game
they play that someone was going to get
fed. Like you didn't know who it was
because they had to like collapse the
pocket. They had to work at the level of
quarterback. They had to work with
overlap. They had to someone had to get
penetration. Someone had to sacrifice.
And they came with that mindset and
they've done it. and Dhorn, Byron, Leo,
like Jay Reed, all of them showed up.
Daw was cool.
>> What does it take to get, you know, you
talk about all of them getting there,
not going to, you know, what does it
take to, you know, get that buy in to
work together, you know, for that?
>> Yeah, it's a good question. Um, it takes
belief in one another. It takes a belief
in one another that we're trying to
actually get something that isn't about
ourselves. It's something that's bigger
than that. and the whole defense has
that.
>> The best thing I done tonight is I sat
on the sideline and I watched Mike lift
the trophy and it was kind of just cool
to take in the moment, sit with my
family and um just smile.
>> I don't know. I have no idea. I'm going
to go back to the locker room, have a
good time.
>> Check your phone. messages?
>> No, I haven't looked at my phone.
Normally, I go in the locker room and I
look at my phone, but I came out. They
were we we um got together as a group
and I came straight over here.
>> Yeah, my mom
call her up.
>> No, I'll wait for her. I ain't going to
call her now. I know she'll be happy
though. But I'm so I'm so excited. She
went to the she went to the party to
watch the game and I just I can't wait
to talk to her.
>> Few more questions, guys.
>> Thanks.
My mom's done everything to get me here.
That was her sole purpose and she done
it.
>> You have a guy like,
>> you know it.
>> Um Oh, it is your all of them. Sam, J,
um K9 and Gray. All all the guys like
this is a team. Mike's created a team
that want to win for each other.
Can you feel it coming out?
>> Yeah, I can. That's why I'm trying to
hold it back. So, like I just want to
get out of
>> Thanks, guys. Thanks very much. I really
appreciate you guys. Thanks.
Just go.